

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details
Shenzhen, China
8613148723062
kuangdan23062@gmail.com

Links

<u>Github</u>

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Instagram</u>

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript, HTML&CSS, Sass, TypeScript, GraphQL

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Vue, jQuery,
Next.js, Node.js, Express,
Koa, Tailwindcss, Styled
Components, Ant Design,
ElementUI

Tools & Platforms

Webpack, Vite, Git

Languages

Mandarin, English

Education

Master Degree, International Relations, China Foreign Affairs University

Profile

I am a web developer over 7 years. I have experiences in the industry of ecommerce and building in-house systems of a large chain supermarket. During my previous career, I have conducted over 10 e-commerce related projects, and more than 5 admin dashboard systems, including pc and mobile oriented web applications. Proficient in an assortment of technologies, including JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Typescript, Node.js, Next.js, Axios, etc. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Employment History

Web Developer, Yonghui Supermarket Corporation, Beijing

OCTOBER 2018 - APRIL 2022

- Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for in-house projects, including monitoring system, shop devices management system, marketing campaign planning system, server management system, etc
- Using different languages, frameworks, and libraries such as JavaScript, React, Redux, Ant Design, TypeScript, Styled Components, Node.js, Vue.js, Vuex, ElementUI, WebSocket
- Communicated with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, product managers on a regular basis
- · Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications

Web Developer, Sao Tianxia, Beijing

JUNE 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed and maintained web applications, mostly mobile oriented, including various QR-code based e-commerce user interfaces
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements
- Worked with Vue.js, Vuex, CSS3, SASS, ElementUI, Webpack, Gulp to build web pages on different sizes of mobile phones
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times

Web Developer, Zhu Baijia, Beijing

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2016

- Built a web application for a hotel and homestay booking platform
- Developed and maintained code primarily using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery
- Worked at an independent level, while also serving as an effective and enthusiastic collaborator

Personal Projects

Chat Room

Sep 2022

A real-time chat room using Express, JWT, Socket.io, React and Tailwindcss

Headless CMS Blog

June 2022

A responsive blog website with featured and recent posts, categories. full markdown articles, author information, comments, etc. Using React, Next.js, GraphQl, Tailwindcss